---
newspaper: Gleiwitzer - Beuthener - Tarnowitzer Heimatblatt
recordId: 010077960_1986
filename: Glei-Beu-TarnHeimatblatt1986-024.xml
newspaperId: 010077960
keywords: Zernitz
---
  
  
Boguschütz-Zalesche, D. u. Col. Krs. Glei- 
witz, P. Tost, A. Slupsko, St. Stadt Tost, Ag. 
Tost, Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Briczow (Boitschow), Forsthaus, Krs, Glei- 
witz, P. Rudschinitz, A. Kieferstädtel, St. 
Rachowitz, Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Boitschow, D. u. G. Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Rud- 
schinitz; A. Kieferstädtel, St. Rachowitz; Ag. 
u. Ldg. Gleiwitz, 
Boniowitz, D. u. Rg. mit Kalksteinbruch, 
Krs. Gleiwitz; P. Peiskretscham, A. u. St. 
Kaminietz, Ag. Preiskretscham, Ldg. Glei- 
witz. 
Borscz, Vw. Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Laband, A. u. 
St. Rzetzitz; Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Brieger Vorwerk, Krs. u. P. Gleiwitz, A. u. 
St. Preiswitz, Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Brodkammer, Vw. Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Peiskret- 
scham, A. Kaminietz, St. Ziewientzitz, Ag. u. 
Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Brynnek (Brynnek), D. u. Rg., Krs. Gleiwitz, 
P. Tworog, A. u. St. Brynneck, Ag. Tarnowitz, 
Ladg. Beuthen. 
Brzesnitza, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Tsorog, A. 
u. St. Brynneck, Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Brzezina, Freigut, Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Tost, A. 
u. St. Stadt Tost, Ag. Tost, Ldg. . 
Brzezinka, D. u. Rg., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. La- 
band, A. Kieferstädtel, St. Koslow I. II. III. 
Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Brzosie, Col., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Peiskret- 
Scham, A. u. St. Bitschin, Ag. Tost, Ldg. Glei- 
witz, 
Buozek, D., Krs. Gleiwitz, siehe Buschek 
Buschek, D., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Rudzinitz, A. 
Bitschin, St. Czechlau, Ag. Tost, Ldg. Glei- 
witz. 
Carlowitz, Col. Krs. u. P. Gleiwitz, A. Schloß 
Kieferstädtel, St. Kozlow, Ag. u. Ldg. Glei- 
witz, . 
Carlshof, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Peiskret- 
scham, jetzt Neuhof genannt. . 
Catharinenhof, Vw., Krs. u. P. Gleiwitz, A. 
u. St. Schalscha, Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Charlottenhof, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Tost, 
A. u. St. Schwieben, Ag. Tost, Ldg. 
Chorisskowitz, Col. Krs. Gleiwitz, P. u. A. 
Kieferstädtel, St. Schloß Kieferstädtel, Ag. 
u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Chwosez, bei Schierot, Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Lan- 
gendorf, A. Schierot, St. Schierot (Schieroth), 
Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Corzawka, Först. Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Kiefer- 
städtel, A. u. St. Schloß Kieferstädtel, Ag. u. 
Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Czakanau, D. u. G., Krs. Gleiwitz, siehe Scha- 
kanau. 
qq 
Czarkow, D. u. G., Krs. Gleiwitz, siehe Schar- 
OW. 
Czechlau (Chechlau), D. u. G., Krs. Gleiwitz, 
P. Rudzinitz, A. Bitschin, St. Czechlau, Ag. 
u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Czechowitz, D. u. G., Krs. Gleiwitz, siehe 
Schechowitz. 
Czerwionka, Col., Krs. Gleiwitz, siehe Scher- 
wionka. 
Czinezella, (Laband), Forsth. Krs. Gleiwitz, 
P. A. u. St. Laband, Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Deutsch-Zernitz, D., Krs. u. P. Gleiwitz, A. 
u. St. Schönwald, Ag. u..Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Dianenberg, Forsthaus u. Forstrevier, Krs. 
Tost-Gleiwitz, A. u. St. Schloß Tost, Ag. Tost, 
Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Dombrowa, Col., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Peiskret- 
scham, A. u. St. Lubie, Ag. Peiskretscham, 
Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Dombrowka, D. u. Rg., Kreis Gleiwitz, A. u. 
St. Schloß Tost, Ag. Tost, Ldg. Gleiwitz, P. 
Tost. 
Dometzko, D. u. Forstrevier, Krs. Gleiwitz, 
P. Tost, A. u. St. Schloß Tost, Ag. Tost, Ldg. 
Gleiwitz. 
Dziedzinka, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Ujest, A. 
Bitschin, St. Chechlau, Ag. Tost, Ldg. Glei- 
witz. 
Dziedzionkau, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Rud- 
zinitz, A. Bitschin, St. Chechlau, Ag. Tost, 
Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Dziersno, Oberu. Nieder, D. u. G. Krs. Glei- 
witz, siehe Sersno. 
Einhof, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Wieschowa, A. 
Kaminietz, St. Zimientzitz, Ag. u. Ldg. Glei- 
witz. 
Ellgoth-Tost, D. u. Rg., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. u: 
A. Groß Kottulin, St. Kottulin, Ag. Tost, Ldg. 
Gleiwitz. 
Ellgoth v. Groeling, D. u. Rg., Krs. Gleiwitz, 
P. Laband, A. Sersno, St. Rzetzitz, Ag. u. Ldg. 
Gleiwitz. . 
Ellgoth-Zabrze, D. Krs. u. P. Gleiwitz, A. u. 
St. Trynnek, Ag. u. Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Elsterberg, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. Peiskret- 
Scham, A. Schierot, St. Pniow, Ag. u. Ldg. 
Gleiwitz. 
Emanuelswunsch, Vw., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. 
Peiskretscham, A. u. St. Lubie, Ag. Peiskret- 
scham, Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Fasannerie, Forsth., Krs. Gleiwitz, P. La- 
band, A. Kieferstädtel, St. Koslow, Ag. u. 
Ldg. Gleiwitz. 
Ferdinandshof, Col., Krs. Gleiwitz, siehe 
Grabina. , 
Fohlung, Vw., Krs, Gleiwitz, P. jetzt Barbara- 
of. .
  